

Software Developer

gheorghebalan.com



balan_gheorghe_89@yahoo.com



+45 27 50 17 69



<u>GitHub</u>

Skills

ASP.NET / .NET Core

Azure Services

MSSQL

Dynamicweb CMS

Umbraco CMS

Sitecore CMS

Javascript

HTML / CSS

Certifications

Sitecore 8 Website Development for .NET Developers - 2016

Language Skills

Danish - working proficiency

English - academic proficiency

Norwegian - casual user

Romanian - native proficiency

Hobbies

Wing Chun

Reading

Travelling

Cycling

SUMMARY

I am a developer with more than five years experience in the field. I like to challenge myself constantly, and to work in a dynamic environment.

I strive to deliver solutions that can be easily maintained, and that create additional value for the clients. I find it valuable to learn from other team members, and to get inspired by them.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Developer Planday

2019 - ongoing

As a back-end developer work with with microservices written in ASP.NET and .NET core. I have practical experience with unit testing and mocking data in xUnit, nUnit, and fixtrues. The apis run in Azure, and I am familiar with Application Insights, CI, event-driven architectrue and blob storage.

System Consultant

Twins

2017 - 2019

As a system consultant I was responsible for developing digital solutions in Dynamicweb and Umbraco CMS. I have hands on experience with Azure Services. I have worked on integrating with Azure Service Bus, Azure Table Storage and with data import from Excel and CSV files.

System Developer Evision

2015 - 2017

I was responsible for maintaining and developing the .NET based e-commerce framework. The framework acts as a bridge between a .NET based CMS system, like Umbraco or Sitecore, aand a Microsft ERP system, such as Navision or C5.

Web Developer Freesoft

2014 - 2015

I have developed Freesoft 3.0, an on-line management, and accounting system for craftsmen. My responsibilities varied from building the GUI of the system, to writing back-end PHP code, managing databases, reading data from external sources, and generating PDF or Excel files.

Web Developer

Intern

Mirsc

As intern in MIRSK, a medium-sized Danish company working with speech reacognition, I have contributed by developing and maintaining e-mail templates using XHTML and Marketo. I have also participated in re-designing the webpage of the company.

EDUCATION

KEA

PBA - Web Development

2014-2015

Copenhagen

A web developer has practical knowledge of building web applications of all sizes. A graduate is trained in working with all the programming aspects of an application from front-end to back-end, as well as databases and deployment.

KEA

AP - Multimedia Design

2012-2014 Copenhagen

UBB

BA -

Human Sciences

2008-2011 Cluj-Napoca A Multimedia Designer has knowledge about marketing, design, coding and organization. Software development methods like SCRUM and Waterfall are used extensively throughout the programme.

A graduate of Humanities has the skills neccessary to express his ideas and thoughts effectively both orally and in writing. The curriculum revolves around the study of grammar, vocabulary, literature and phonetics of the aforementioned languages.